Finding Aid for the Ojai Music Festival Records PASC-M.0277
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Festival Recordings and Artist Interviews, 1940s-1980s; Series 1.
  - Ojai 8703, May 30, 1987; one sound reel (Box 96, Folder 2)
    Program $8703 Del Tredici, Varese Master, stereo, dolby
  - Ojai 8703, one sound reel (Box 96, Folder 5)
    Ojai 8703 Steiger/La Barbara Reel 1 of 2
    This reel does not have a pre-printed production label on it.
  - Ojai 8703, one sound reel (Box 96, Folder 6)
    Ojai 8703 Foss/Copland Reel 2 of 2
  - Ojai 8703 Ambience, 5-30-87; Reel (Box 66, Folder 19)
    Ojai 8703 Tape 469 Ambience
  - Ojai 8703 Ambience 2, 5-30-87; reel (Box 66, Folder 20)
    Ojai 8703 Tape 469 Ambience #2
  - Ojai 8704, 5-31-87?; reel (Box 66, Folder 12)
    No program list or sticker with further information.
  - Ojai 8704 Ambience, 5-31-87; reel (Box 66, Folder 21)
    Ojai 8704 Ambience Tape 469
    No reel number
  - Ojai 8704 Ravel, La Valse, Liszt, 6-1-86; Sound reel in cardboard box (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Reel 4, Program #8704, Tape #469.
    Sticker on reel says: 10 Mix Master LAPO REEL.
  - Ojai 8704 Reel 1 of 2, 05-30-87; Reel on metal spool in box (Box 68, Folder 11)
    8704 Reel 1 of 2
    No program listing
  - Ojai 8705 Ambience, 5-31-87; reel (Box 66, Folder 22)
    Ojai 8795 Tape 469 Ambience
  - Ojai 8705 Reel 1 of 3, Reel on plastic spool in box (Box 68, Folder 12)
    8705 1 of 3
    No program list or sticker.
  - Ojai 8705 Reel 2 of 3, 5-31-87; Reel in plastic, on plastic spool in box (Box 68, Folder 13)
    8705 2 of 3 Foss
  - Ojai 8705 Reel 3 of 3, 5-31-87; Reel in plastic, on plastic spool in box (Box 68, Folder 14)
    8705 3 of 3
  - Ojai 8706 Harbison, 6-2-85; Sound reel in cardboard box (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Reel, Program #8705, Tape #469. 1 of 4.
    Label has Vivaldi crossed off after Harbison.
  - Ojai Ambience, 4-4-90; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Tape 806 Length: 1:08
    No program number.
  - Ojai Fest 83 Swanne Alley Segments 1,2, 6-4-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Sticker says Swanne Salley Segments 1, 2, 3 and the 3 is crossed out.
    - Shubert Songs, 1983 June 5; uclapasc0277_019_008; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:22:04) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 8)
      Content note: Program #3, Tape 250, Reel 2 of 3
  - Ojai fest. 82 Beethoven, 12-2-82; Sound reel in plastic and styrofoam casing (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Reel 2 of 5; Program #2; no tape #
    Length: 19:37
  - Ojai fest. 82 Debussy, 12-2-82; Sound reel in plastic and styrofoam casing (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Reel 4 of 5; Program #2; no tape #
    Length: 18:50
  - Ojai fest. 82 Mozart, 12-2-82; Sound reel in styrofoam casing (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Reel 1 of 5; Program #2; no tape #.
    Length: 16:46
  - Ojai fest. 82 Stravinsky. Concerto 2 Solo Piano, 12-2-82; Sound reel in styrofoam casing (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Reel 3 of 5; Program #2; no tape #.
    Length: 25:48
  - Ojai fest. 82 Stravinsky: Petrouchka, 12-2-82; Sound reel in plastic and styrofoam casing (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Reel 5 of 5; Program #2; no tape #
    Length: 18:52
  - Ojai Festival 1979 "Lehrstueck" Hindemith, Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 9)
    "Tape of May 20, 1979 performance of Hindemith's work, Lehrstueck with the Festival Chamber Orchestra the direction of Lukas Foss. Werner Klemperer, narrator. Audience participation. (clown scene deleted from tape)."
  - Ojai Festival 1981 Reel 1 of 4, May 1981; Reel in styrofoam with plastic; production notes; program (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Reel. Information from Tape Log Form: Reel 1: Six German Dances, K509, Mozart Reel 2: Our Hunting Fathers, Britten Reel 3: Symphony #4 in D major, Clementi Reel 4: Remainder of symphony
    Recording and programs from the 35th Annual Ojai Music Festival.
  - Ojai Festival 1981 Reel 2 of 4, May 1981; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Reel 2 of 4.
  - Ojai Festival 1981 Reel 3 of 4, May 1981; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Reel 3 of 4.
  - Ojai Festival 1981 Reel 4 of 4, May 1981; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Reel 4 of 4.
  - Ojai Festival 82 Program #2, 1982; 2 KUSC memos with program information (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Two pages outlining program--accompanies reels in this box 2 copies of memo
    5 reels totaling 1:39:06 Reel 1: Mozart-Fantasy in F minor, K.608 Reel 2: Beethoven-The Grosse Fuge, Op.133 Reel 3: Stravinsky-Concerto for Two Solo Pianos Reel 4: Debussy-Suite "En Blanc et Noir" Reel 5: Stravinsky-Three scenes from Petrouchka
  - Ojai Festival Orchestra May 30, 1981, Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 17)
    Telemann, Mozart, Riegger, Ives
    American debut of pianist Peter Nagy
  - Ojai Festival Outreach Program A Nouveau Rick Production, 1988; VHS tape (Box 47, Folder 3)
    VHS tape of outreach? Running time 8 minutes.
    - Ojai 8703, 1988 April 14; uclapasc0277_047_003; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:38:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 3)
      Content Note: KUSC: Steiger, La Barbara, Foss, Copland
  - Ojai Festivals Ltd 82 A-83-122838, 1982; Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Side 1: Stravinsky-Babin: Three Pieces from Petrushka Side 2: Stravinsky: Symphony in 3 mvts
    Paul Jacobs and Gilbert Kalish, piano Ojai Festival Orchestra
  - Ojai Festivals Ltd 82 A-84-145110, 1981; Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Works by Riegger, Ives, Telemann, Mozart Performances by Ray Brown All-Stars
  - Ojai Festivals Ltd 81, 1981; Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 16)
    Only information: Recorded by Steven Barker
  - Ojai Festivals 84 AAD-559, June 1984; Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Performers: Pierre Boulez, LA Philharmonic. Works by: Ravel, Boulez, Stravinsky
  - Ojai Music Fest 83 Martinu Concerto for 2 String Orch, 9-27-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Reel 1 of 2; Program #5; no tape #
  - Ojai Music Fest 83 Smetana, 9-27-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing; production form (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Reel 2 of 2; Program #5; tape #250
    Production Quality Control Form: Airday 9/29/83 Program length: 1 hour, 5 minutes, 12 seconds Program: Martinu; Smetana-Szell
  - Ojai Music Festival 1983 Program #5, 9/13/83; KUSC memo (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Memo
    Covers program #5, 2 reels. Reel 1: Martinu-Concerto for Two String Orch Reel 2: Smetana-String Quartet "In My Life" Orchestration by George Szell Total time: 1:05:12
  - Ojai Music Festival 565, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Robert Craft, music director and conductor. Includes excerpts of works by: Stravinsky, Beethoven, Stravinsky, Bobby Hutcherson.
  - Ojai Sample Tape June 4/5 & 7 1982, 1975; Reel (Box 63, Folder 91)
    Info on box: 7 1/2 IPS 1/2 TR Stereo
  - Ojai, 1983 Festival, 8-31-85; Memo and production notes (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Two papers
    Memo covers Program #4 of '83 Festival. 4 reels totaling 1:34:01. No song titles, just "sets 1-7" Production notes say airdate 9/22/83
    - Swanne Alley Segments, 1983 June 5; uclapasc0277_019_007; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:30:07) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 7)
      Content note: Program #4, Reel 4 of 4, Tape 226
  - Outs, 1983 August 30; open reel audio tape (Box 8, Folder 8)
    On item: Reel, Program #4, Tape #250.
  - Outtakes Amb 1 Ojai 82, 1982; Reel on plastic spool (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Reel: program 1
    Not in styrofoam, plastic or box.
  - Pac Horizon Four Ojai 8602 1 of 3, 5-31-86; 4-21-87; Scotch reel with production sheet (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Program 8602; Tape 469 Reel 1
    KUSC info: Pacific Horizon Four (Ojai 8602) Three reels, original KUSC airdate 4-23-87 Reel 1: Boulez, Kernis Reel 2: Carter Reel 3: Copland Total time: 1-26:12
  - Pac Horizon Four Ojai 8602 2 of 3, 5-31-86; Scotch reel (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Program 8602; Tape 469 Reel 2
  - Pac Horizon Four Ojai 8602 3 of 3, 5-31-86; Scotch reel (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Program 8602; Tape 469 Reel 3
  - Pac Horizon Seven Ojai 8605 1 of 3, June 1, 1986; 5-14-87; AGFA reel with program list (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Tape no. 469; Program 8605 1 of 3
    Program: Pacific Horizon 7 Aired on KUSC 5-14-87 Three reels Reel 1: Kurtag Reel 2: Kurtag, Schoenberg Reel 3: Beethoven Total: 1:28:40
  - Pac Horizon Seven Ojai 8605 2 of 3, June 1, 1986; Reel (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Tape no. 469; Program 8605 2 of 3
  - Pac Horizon Seven Ojai 8605 3 of 3, June 1, 1986; AGFA Reel (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Tape no. 469; Program 8605 3 of 3
  - Pac Horizon Six Ojai 8604 1 of 5, 6-1-86; 5-87; 10-7-87; Scotch reel with production sheet (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Program 8604 Tape 469 Reel 1
    KUSC info: Pacific Horizon Six Ojai 8604 5 reels Reel 1: Schumann Reel 2: Schumann, Kurtag Reel 3: Carter Reel 4: Ravel, Liszt Reel 5: Debussy Total time: 1:52:34
  - Pac Horizon Six Ojai 8604 3 of 5, 6-1-86; Scotch reel (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Program 8604 Tape 469 Reel 3
  - Pac Horizon Six Ojai 8604 5 of 5, 6-1-86; Scotch reel (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Program 8604 Tape 469 Reel 5
  - Pac Horizon Three 1 of 4, 5-29-86; 4-14-87; Reel with production list (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Program 8601; Tape 469 Reel 1 of 4
    Contents of reels: Pacific Horizon Three (Ojai Vestibule 1) KUSC airdate: 4-16-87 Reel 1: Evans, Monk, Glass Reel 2: Kurtag, Graves Reel 3: Reiley Reel 4: Shostakovich, Hendrix Total: 1:55:56
  - Pac Horizon Three 2 of 4, 5-29-86; Reel (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Program 8601; Tape 469 Reel 2 of 4
  - Pac Horizon Three 3 of 4, 5-29-86; Reel (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Program 8601; Tape 469 Reel 3 of 4
  - Pac Horizon Three 4 of 4, 5-29-86; Reel (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Program 8601; Tape 469 Reel 4 of 4
  - Pac Horizon Vive Ojai 8603 Reel 1 of 4, 5-30-86;10-7-87; Reel with production note (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Reel Program 8603 Tape 469 Reel 1
    Contents Reel 1: Stravinsky, Adams, Mozart Reel 2: Stravinsky Los Angeles Philharmonic
  - Pac Horizon Vive Ojai 8603 Reel 2 of 4, 5-30-86; 4-28-87; Reel with production note (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Reel Program 8603 Tape 469 Reel 2
    Contents Pacific Horizon 5ive 4 reels 1: Stravinsky, Adams 2: Mozart 3: Stravinsky 4: Stravinsky Total time: 1:24:54
  - Pac Horizon Vive Ojai 8603 Reel 3 of 4, 5-30-86; Reel (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Reel Program 8603 Tape 469 Reel 3
  - Pac Horizon Vive Ojai 8603 Reel 4 of 4, 5-31-86; Reel (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Reel Program 8603 Tape 469 Reel 4
  - Petrouchka, 1982 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 17, Folder 9)
    On item: Reel 5 of x; Tape #2.
  - Piano Concerto, 1982 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 20, Folder 10)
    On item: Reel 4 of 4; tape #1.
  - Pierre Boulez Tape, June 1-3, 1984; Cassette tape (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Pierre Boulez and Los Angeles Philharmonic Debussy: Finale from Sonata for Flute, Viola and Harp Boulez: Eclat/Mutliples Ravel: Ma Mere l'Oye
    Says Dolby B.
    - Ojai 8702, 1988 April 7; uclapasc0277_047_002; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:47:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 2)
      Content Note: KUSC: Bach, Wuorinen, Handel
  - Production and cue sheets, June 1983; papers (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Script for Shankar performance (to be broadcast on KUSC) and production memo.
    Order: 4 reels: Program 1 (Ravi Shankar) 1. Rag Hameer 35:20 2. Raga Kamage 28:25 3. Raga Malkounze 35:43 4. Raga Mishragada 32:29 Total length: 2:11:53
  - Production Cue Sheets, 1982 June; papers (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Programs:Friday night-- Mozart, Magic Flute March Starzer- Gluck, Divertimento -- Haydn, Divertimento -- Stravinsky, Octet Gabrieli, Canzone. Stravinsky, Symphonies Stravinsky, Concerto Saturday afternoon-- Mozart, Fantasy K.608 Beethoven, Grosse Fuge Stravinsky, 2 piano concerto Debussy, En Blanc Stravinsky, Petrouchka
    Production info for 1982 recordings.
  - Production lists and scripts Ojai 8703, 1988; papers (Box 56, Folder 1)
    KUSC production sheet Scripts (with edits) for radio broadcasts
    Contents 8703; 2 reels KUSC airdate: 4-18-88 Reel 1: Steiger, La Barbara Reel 2: Foss, Copland Total--54:45
  - Production memos and lists, 1988-1989; Memos and program lists (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Memos from KUSC and program lists.
    Contents: KUSC memos for Programs 8701, 8702, 8703, 8704, 8705 (correspond with reels and DATS) Program lists are unnumbered but for 1989 season (June 2-4, 1989)
    - Ojai 8705, 1988 May 2; uclapasc0277_047_005; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:19:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 5)
      Content Note: KUSC: Messiaen, Handel, Couperin, Hill, Jannequin, Biggs, Del Tredici
  - Production Sheets Ojai 83 Programs 2 and 3, 1983; papers (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Production cue sheets for Ojai 83 programs 2 and 3 recordings. Corresponds with reels in same box.
    Program 2: Henze, Kennon, Riley, Sallinen, Shostakovich Program 3: Stravinsky, Schubert, Milhaud
    - Henze, 1983 June 4; uclapasc0277_055_001; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:25:03) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 1)
      Content Note: Program #2, Tape #250
  - Program information: Ojai 1982-83, 9-27-83; 3 program memos (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Memo 1. Festival 82, Program 1. 4 reels. Reel 1: Starzer/Gluck, Gabrieli, Haydn. Reel 2: Mozart, Stravinsky Reel 3: Stravinsky Reel 4: Stravinsky (total: 1:31:33) Memo 2. Ojai 83, Program 2; 4 reels. Reel 1: Henze Reel 2: Kennon Reel 3: Riley, Salinen Reel 4: Shostakovich, Adams (total: 1:49:32) Memo 3. 83 Festival Program 3. 3 reels. Reel 1: Stravinsky Reel 2: Schubert Reel 3: Milhaud (total: 1:18:07)
  - Programs and production lists, 1972-1994; papers and programs (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Production lists for reels and DATs, photocopies of programs from 1972-1994, published program from 1987.
  - Puppets African Ray Pizzi, May 1978; moving image (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Reel with synopsis. Synopsis explains Master Peter's Puppet Show.
    - Carol Wincenc Interview, 1972 May 30; uclapasc0277_063_002; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:14:43) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 2)
      Conditions Governing Access
  - Quartet no.8, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 4)
    On item: Program #2, Reel 4 of 4. Duration: 30:11
  - R.C.'s Vox Trax, 1983 August 25; open reel audio tape (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ravi Shankar, June, 2, 1983; 1 sound tape reel, 10" (Box 35, Folder 1)
    On reel, "Reel 1 of, Program #1."
  - Ravi Shankar Part 1, 1983 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 11)
    On item: Program #2, Reel 1 of 4.
  - Ravi Shankar Part 1, 1983 August 10; open reel audio tape (Box 35, Folder 8)
    On item: Program #1, Tape #250, Reel 1 of 2.
  - Reel script, August 1983; Photocopied papers (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Photocopies of KUSC script and music information for an Ojai reel. Papers are separate from reels in box; unclear which reel matches script.
  - Rich's Voice Tracks, September 6, 1983; Sound reel in styrofoam casing (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Reel with printout of musical order and script, for use on KUSC.
  - Rich's Vox Trax, 1982 April 23; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Reel with script for radio broadcast: Paul Jacobs/Gilbert Kalish, piano; Mozart, Beethoven, Debussy, Stravinsky.
    On item: Ojai 82, program 2.
  - Rich's Vox Trax, 1982 November 17; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Reel with script for radio broadcast: Starzer-Gluck/Gabriel/Haydn/Mozart/Stravinsky.
    On item: Ojai 82, program 1,Rich's Vox Trax,Reel 1 of 1.
  - Riley & Sullivan, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 5)
    On item: Reel 3 of 4. Duration: 30:11
  - Schoenberg: Chamber Symphony op.9, 6-2-84; reel (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Ojai 8401 Reel 2 of 4
  - Schoenberg: Song of Wood Dove, 6-2-84; 9-6-84; Reel and production list (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Ojai 8401 Concert 3 1 of 4
    Program list: 4 reels 1: Schoenberg 2: Schoenberg 3: Boulez 4: Stravinsky 1:53:22
  - Shankar Outs #1, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 35, Folder 6)
    On item: 1 of 3.
  - Shankar Outs #1, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 35, Folder 7)
    On item: 3 of 3.
  - Shankar Part 1, 1983 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 10)
    On item: Program #2, Reel 2 of 4.
  - Shankar-2nd half, 1983 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 8)
    On item: Program #1, Reel 4 of 4.
  - Songs, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 1)
    On item: Program #3.Reel 2 of 3.
  - Stravinsky/Mozart/Starzer/Gluck/Haydn/Garbricle[?], 1982 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 17, Folder 6)
    On item: Reel 1 of 4; Tape #1. Note says: Airdate 11/22/82; Timing: 1:31:33; along with repeated information from sticker; also includes Production Cue Sheet.
  - Stravinsky: Histoire du Soldat, 6-3-84; reel (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Ojai 8401 Reel 3 of 4
  - Swan Alley/Amb II, 1983 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Symphony for Wind, 1982 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 17, Folder 8)
    On item: Reel 3 of 4; Tape #1.
  - Takemitsu, 6-1-85; reel (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Ojai 8502 Reel 2 of 4
    Reel 3 of 4 is not in this box.
  - The Schubertians Director: Dr. Zytowski USC Santa Barbara, 1975; Scotch magnetic tape (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Reel with index card (contents)
    Box says: Tape--Copy made by W. Price--For Festival Use
  - Winter Int 2 Foss Int, 1983?; Reel on plastic spool (Box 63, Folder 3)
    No production information. Sticker on reel is from KUSC.
    - Carol Wincenc Interview; Lukas Foss Interview, 1972 May 30; uclapasc0277_063_003; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:15:42) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 3)
      Part 1: Carol Wincenc Interview; Part 2: Lukas Foss Interview
- Artist Biographies and Contracts, 1940s-1980s; Series 2.
  - Bang on a Can, 1987-1989; press clippings, correspondence, programs (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Related to marathon performances by Bang on a Can and endorsement letters from John Cage, etc.
  - Biegel--Conductors Circle--9/15/90, September, 1990; photographs, programs, papers (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Biographical information about pianist Jeffrey Biegel, who performed for a donor event.
  - BMI/AFTRA, 1991; papers (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Contracts and correspondence with BMI (Broadcast Music Inc) and AFTRA (American Federation of Television and Radio Artists)
  - Boulez, May, 1989; news clippings, program, photocopies (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Related to Festival Boulez, held at UCLA's Royce Hall in May of 1989.
  - California E.A.R. Unit; Canadian Music Centre, 1988-1989; papers (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Repertoire for the California E.A.R. Unit; information about the Prairie Regional Director of the Canadian Music Centre in Calgary
  - Contracts Artists, 6/4-6/6/93; Contracts, correspondence (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Drafts and final contracts with artists for 93 Festival
  - Contracts Music & Instruments, 1991; papers (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Correspondence and contracts with musicians and composers for the 1991 Festival.
  - Davies, Peter Maxwell, 1991; papers, brochures (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Biographies and information about British composer Peter Maxwell Davies.
  - Davies, Peter Maxwell Correspondence 89-90 Season, 1989-1990; papers (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Correspondence with Davies/his management team and Ojai staff regarding Davies' appointment with the Festival.
  - Diane Wittry, 1988-1989; Photographs, news clippings, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Biographical sketch and reviews of conductor Diane Wittry, who was associate conductor in 1988.
  - Elliott Carter, 1988-1994; photographs, biographies, news clippings (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Related to the 80th Birthday of composer Elliott Carter, feted at Tanglewood, San Francisco, London and New York. Also composer in residence at Ojai.
  - Ernest Fleischmann, 1989; Press clippings, biographical sketches (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Los Angeles Times magazine cover story about LA Philharmonic conductor Ernest Fleischmann; press release
  - Ferguson; Fierro; Foss, 1980-1990; photographs, biographies, correspondence (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Photographs and biographical information about flutist Janet Ferguson, pianist Charles Fierro and composer/conductor Lukas Foss.
  - Festival '91 Contracts, 1991; papers (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Artist contracts for '91 Festival.
  - Frederic Rzewski; Esa-Pekka Salonen, 1989, 1992; photographs, biographical sketches, news clippings, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Biographical information about composer Frederic Rzewski; article from the Los Angeles Times Magazine about Finnish conductor Esa-Pekka Salonen
  - Giles; Grierson, 1994; photographs, biographies, news clippings (Box 49, Folder 9)
    Information about flutist Anne Diener Gilles and keyboardist Ralph Grierson.
  - Gloria Cheng; Stephen Colburn, 1986-1993; photographs, biographies, news clippings (Box 48, Folder 9)
    Biographical information about pianist Gloria Cheng and oboist Stephen Colburn.
  - Gyorgy Ligeti, 1989; Biography (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Biography of Hungarian composer Gyorgy Ligeti.
  - Harbison '91, 1991; papers (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, contracts, and information about the use of a Harbison piece at Ojai.
  - Heidi Lesemann and Dr. F. Lesemann, 1972-1978; Photographs, correspondence (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Regards the employment of Dr. Frederick Lesemann and then his wife as Production Manager of the Ojai Festival in 1973-74.
  - Instrumentalists Festival '91, 1991; papers (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Schedules and rehearsal information for instrumentalists of the festival.
  - James Busterud, 1988; photographs, biographies, news clippings (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Information about the baritone singer.
  - Jazz at Ojai, 1984; papers (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Contracts, plans, programs related to the Jazz at Ojai program in 1984.
  - Jazz at Ojai, 1983; papers (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Contracts, plans, programs related to the Jazz at Ojai program in 1983.
  - Joann Falletta, 1990; biographical information (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Information about the conductor.
  - John Adams, 1992-1994; news clippings, photocopies, correspondence (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Biographies and information about John Adams
  - John Aler tenor, 1991-1992; photographs, news clippings, correspondence (Box 39, Folder 12)
    Biographical information about tenor John Aler.
  - John Bruce Yeh, 1980's?; photographs, biographical sketches (Box 39, Folder 17)
    Information about clarinetist John Bruce Yeh, at the time a member of the Chicago Symphony.
    No date on bio--refers to JBY having been on DePaul's faculty since 1979.
  - Johnson, Thor, 1940s-1950s; press kit, photographs (Box 49, Folder 13)
    Related to conductor Thor Johnson and his engagement at Ojai.
  - Kent Nagano; Mel Powell, 1990?; photographs and brochure (Box 38, Folder 16)
    Photograph of Kent Nagano. Brochure about composer Mel Powell written by Schirmer Music.
  - Kevin McMillan, photographs (Box 39, Folder 19)
    Headshots of Kevin McMillan, baritone.
  - Kronos, 1984-1985; photographs, biographies, news clippings (Box 50, Folder 2)
    Regarding famous Kronos Quartet.
    Large folder.
  - Kronos Quartet, 1992-1993; press kit (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Photographs, articles and other information provided by Kronos Quartet for festival
  - La Barbara, Joan, 1992; photographs, biographies, news clippings (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Regards American composer/vocalist Joan La Barbara.
  - LA Master Chorale; Harbison score, 1991; papers (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Contracts and correspondence with the LA Master Chorale; copy of Harbison vocal score for the LA Master Chorale's performance
  - LA Philharmonic New Music Group, 1991; Biographies (Box 39, Folder 11)
    Information about the LA Philharmonic New Music Group, including trumpeter Boyde Hood. Also includes discography of the group.
  - LA Philharmonic Orchestra, 1970-1990; correspondence, programs (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Related to performances of the LA Philharmonic at Ojai during the 1970s.